Guide to the NURTUREart records CBHM.0025
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 1: Artists' Registry
  - Sub-series 1.1: A-Z Files
    - Ferreira de Araujo, Fernando, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Ferro John, circa 2006 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Fetta, Richard, circa 2004 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Fichter, Toma, circa 2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Field, Jon, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Fine, Joan, circa 2005 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Fisher, Deborah, circa 2004 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Fitelson, Mike, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Fitzgerald, Karen, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Fleisher, Fred, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Flunker, Barb, circa 2007 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Fontaine, Viva, circa 2006 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Ford, Monique, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Formica, Jennifer, circa 2007 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Forrest, Margaret, circa 2004 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Forsberg, Dana, circa 2008 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Foster, Catherine, circa 2004 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Forth, Clyde, circa 2006 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Foss, David, circa 2006 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Fourie, Marianne, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Fournier, Nicole, circa 2007 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Fowler, Gabriel, circa 2007 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Fowlkes, Stephan, circa 2007 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Frank, David, circa 2000 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Fankel, Larry S., circa 2002 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Fraser, Amy E., circa 2005 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Fraser, Annie, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Frater, Jean Alexander, circa 2008 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Frazelle, Travis, circa 2006 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Freder, Gudrun, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Friedman, Lynne, circa 2007 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Frick, Michelle, circa 2008 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Friedmann, Lynne, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Friedman, Sabra, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Fuentes Walker, Gina, circa 2005 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Fuhrman, Andrea, circa 2005 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Fukushima, Yoko, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Furness, Melissa, circa 2007 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Gaebe, Carly, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Gagnon, Mark, circa 2007 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Gall, Jonathon, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Ganjian, Jesse Lambert and Linda, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Gannis, Carla, circa 2004 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Ganser, Julie, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Garbini, Adrienne E., circa 2007 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Garbani, Isabelle, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Garcia Colvin, Laurel, circa 2009 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Garfinkel, J.J., circa 2004 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Garrison, Richard, circa 2007 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Gaskill, Jay, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Gaynes-Bachman Robin, circa 2004 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Gaz, Stan, circa 2007 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Geering, Mary Louise, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Gelenian-Wood, Terri, circa 2006 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Gennaro, Irene, circa 2005 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Georg, Christy, circa 2010 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - George, Michael, circa 2005 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Gerchick, Anina, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Gerwin, Daniel, circa 2006 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Giacoletti, Larry, circa 2004 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Giancoli, Mary Teresa, circa 2006 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Gianchristiano, Michael, circa 2004 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Gibellini, Laura F., 2008 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Gilbert, David, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Giles, Michael, circa 2008 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Gillis, Andrew, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Giordano, Joan, circa 2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Gitelson, Jonathan, circa 2008 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Giugni, Natalie, circa 2008 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Glasser, Cora Jane, circa 2008 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Gluckman, Galia, circa 2006 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Goetz, Monika, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Golba, Bill, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Goldberg, Ariel, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Goldman, Ben, circa 2007 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Goldman, Toby, circa 2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Goldner, Janet, circa 2004 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Goldstein, Abby, circa 2007 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Gomez, Lucia, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Gordon, Andrea, circa 2004 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Gordon, Irv, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Gordon, Kay, circa 2005 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Gottesfeld, Linda, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Gould, Meggan, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Graham, Eric, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Graminski, Mimi Czajka, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Grant, Lou, circa 2006 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Grant, Robert, circa 2001 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Greene, Talia, circa 2008 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Greenwald, Nick, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Greenwood, Norma, circa 2006 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Grier, Gary, circa 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Griggs, Linda, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Grill, Clare, circa 2008 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Grimyser, Jennifer, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Groupp, Douglas, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Grossman, Naomi, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Groux, Nadja, circa 2004 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Grubin, Joan, circa 2003 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Gubin, Mikhail, circa 2006 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Gulledge, Laura Lee, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Gul-Ses, Soren, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Gundersen, Christina, circa 2009 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Hackemann, Rebecca, circa 2008 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Hagerty, Chris, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Hagy, Kathryn, circa 2002 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Hahn, Ted, circa 2007 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Hale, Josey, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Hall, Ronald L., 2004 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Hallier, Valerie, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Hampshire, John, circa 2005 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Han, Juye, circa 2003 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Han, Yoon Jeong, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Handel, Jon, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Handleman, Janice, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Handon, G.L., circa 2004 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Hargreaves, Jessica, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Harlan, Charles, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Harmon, Erin J., circa 2006 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Harrington, Lisa, circa 2006 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Harris, Emily, circa 2010 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Harris, Mark, circa 2002 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Hart, Tracy, circa 2007 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Havey, Hillary, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Harvey, Own Daniel, circa 2006 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Hauben, Daniel, circa 2003 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Hauk Weiss, Joey, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Haven, Shelley, circa 2006 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Hayden, Martha, circa 2005 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Hayeur, Isabelle, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Hays, Jodi, circa 2009 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Healy, Coleen, circa 2005 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Hecht, Sheila, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Heffernan, Lisa, circa 2001 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Heginbotham, Jan, circa 2001 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Heidel, Gail, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Heins, Tim, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Herman, Molly, circa 2005 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Herman, Rebecca and Shoffner, Mark, circa 2006 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Herman, Robert, circa 2003 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Hernandez, Monica, circa 2007 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Herndon, John, circa 2005 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Hertog, Amy Chappell, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Herzog, Richard A., circa 2008 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Hester, Nathaniel, circa 2008 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Hewko, Mark S., 2008 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Higgens, Katy, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Hildwine, Jeriah, circa 2008 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Hillinger, Edith, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Hinds, Rene, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Hinebrook, Michelle, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Hines, Rachel, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Hinton, Megan, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Hiratsuka, Yuji, circa 2006 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Hirschl, Tamar, circa 2006 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Hobson, Diana, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Hoey, Wayne, circa 2001 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Hoffman, Eileen, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Hofman, Melani, circa 2004 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Hoge, Virginia, circa 2004 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Hoguet, Diedre, circa 2005 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Holder, Ralvin, circa 2007 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Holleman, Kim, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Holmberg, James, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Holmes, Elizabeth, circa 2004 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Holub, Joel, circa 2005 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Holzman, Dara, circa 2005 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Hong, Seon Jang, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Hoogenboom, Jan, circa 2005 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Horochowski, Alexa, circa 2006 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Horvat, Olga, circa 2001 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Horvitz, David, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Houshmand, Roshan, circa 2007 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Howard, Joshua, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Hrbacek, Mary, circa 2007 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Hubard, Olga, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Hüther, Tim Patrick, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Icart-Pierre, Jean Patrick, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Ikens, Curt M., circa 2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Ilnseher, Francois, circa 2006 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Im, Sang-Bin, circa 2006 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Inga, Margaret, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Insogna, Liz, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Irons, Ellie, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Isaievych, Alexandra, circa 2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Ishida, Jun'ichiro, circa 2006 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Ishino, Mayumi, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Cat, circa 2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Jackson, Stephanie, circa 2007 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Jacobson, Gary, circa 2001 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Jager, Britta Melanie, circa 2007 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Jain, Vandana, circa 2005 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Jantzen, Ellen, circa 2009 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Jasmin, Michael, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Jaworski, Janusz, circa 2003 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Jelsma, Amparo, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Jennis, Stevan, circa 2007 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Jensen, Diana, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Jensen, Joelle, circa 2006 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Jensen, Vibeke, circa 2007 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Jeon, Bum-Joo, circa 2004 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Jerinic, Katarina, circa 2007 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Jibilian, Aram, circa 2000 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Jimenez, Jabiel, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Jo, Suejin, circa 2002 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Jobe, Brian, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Johng, Steven, circa 2001 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Christopher M.H., 2008 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, Nikki, circa 2003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Johnson, Isehai, circa 2006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Johnson-Williams, Judy, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Johnston, Grant Lincoln, circa 2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Jones, Oliver, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Jordan, Elizabeth, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Joy, Christopher, circa 2001 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Joynes, Les, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Julig, Sarah, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Kackar-Demirel, Yasemin, circa 2008 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Kahn, Ellen, circa 2002 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Kallio, Harri, circa 2004 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Kalman, Lauren, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Kane, Bonnie, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Kang Wook, Lee, circa 2005 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Kansara, Gautam, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Kao, Jianfone, circa 2005 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Katz, Marie Christine, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Katz, Ruth, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Kaufmann, Elaine, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Kaulaca, Vineta, circa 2008 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Kayes, Debra, circa 2003 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Kayne, Elanit, circa 2001 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Keating, Andrew, circa 2002 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Keegan, Alessandro, circa 2007 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Keeney, Matthew, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Keffer, Mark, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Kelley, Millar, circa 2005 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Kellner, Lisa, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Kellner, Tatana, circa 2007 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Kelly, Todd, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Kelty, Jamie, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Kenan, Ken, circa 2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Kephart, Amy, circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Kerr Jr., William, circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Keshtkar, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Kessler, Greg, circa 2002 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Kiba, Hiromi, circa 2001 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Kiernan, Scott, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Kiley, Ana Garces, circa 2008 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Kim, Gyoung Sun, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Kim, Ha Rhin, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Kim, Jen, circa 2006 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Kim, Jun-Ah, circa 2006 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Kim, Sky, circa 2005 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Kim, Yeon Jin, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Kindermann, Tine, circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - King, Anki, circa 2007 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - King, Carter, circa 2005 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - King, David, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - King, Kathleen, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - King, Mark A., circa 2008 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Kjok, Solveig, circa 2006 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Klar, Sara, circa 2004 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Klare, Dustin, circa 2006 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Klein, Joanne, circa 2004 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Klemperer, Wendy, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Klineman, Peggy, circa 2007 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Klos, Matt, circa 2007 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Kneisel, Leslie, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Knight, Kristy, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Knight, Nicholas, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Knowles, Elizabeth, circa 2008 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Ko, Woon Won, circa 2005 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Kobayashi, Sonomi, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Kobayshi, Yukie, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Koegel, Charles, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Kogan, Leonard, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Komiya, Yaeko, circa 2005 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Kondo, Takeshi, circa 2000 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Konsterlie, Peter, circa 2006 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Koon, Anna, circa 2006 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Koren, Gabriel, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Kotak, Marni, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Kotvics, Katalin, circa 2000 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Kotler, Arcady, circa 2006 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Kotzer, Ann, circa 1998 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Kouns, Marjorie, circa 2002 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Krakauer, Dorothy A., circa 2005 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Krapp, Jose, circa 2000 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Krasner, Jenny, circa 2003 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Krebs, Peter, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Krieger, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Kriese, Niki, circa 2003 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Krugman, Jason, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Krumenacker, Michael, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Kuckelkorn, Ed, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Kun, Shay, circa 2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Kuo, Nina, circa 2002 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Kupferberg, Amy, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Kuriloff, Nina, circa 2001 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Kuroo, Hiroshi, circa 2003 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Kurtzman, Todji, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - La Gamba, Laurent, circa 2004 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - La Porta, Tina, circa 2003 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Label, Eliot, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Laden, Jenny, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Laha, Prasenjit, circa 2006 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Laliberte, Jsun, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Lambert, Emily Noelle, circa 2005 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Lambert, Jesse, circa 2006 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Lamberti, Lucia, circa 2004 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Lande, Vinod, circa 2000 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Landes, Barbara, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Landmer, Rebecca, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Langerman, Elaine, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Lanina, Yuliya, circa 2006 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Lantow, David, circa 2003 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - La Riviere, Mark, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Larko, Valeri, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Latta, William, circa 2005 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Lavatelli, Mark, circa 2005 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Lawrence, Joseph, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Leach, Ron, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Leaness, Leslye, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Lebenkoff, Ethel, circa 2006 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - LeBorious, Meghan, circa 2004 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Leddy, Norene, circa 2003 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Lederberg, Dov, circa 2000 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Lee, Billie, circa 2007 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Lee, Deanna C., 2007 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Lee, Eric Jiaju, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Lee, Eva, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Lee, Haejae, circa 2006 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Lee, Jamie M., 2007 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Lee, Jeesoo, circa 2006 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Lee, Jeesoo, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Lee, Jee Yun, circa 2007 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Lee, Jisoo, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Lee, Numyi, circa 2006 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Lee, Sandra Eula, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Lee, Seung Jun, circa 2000 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Lee, Tom, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Leech, Gwyneth, circa 2003 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Lehman, Wendy, circa 2000 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Leibowitz, Adela, circa 2006 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Leibowitz, Bonny, circa 2005 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Leis, Marietta P., circa 2004 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Leitao, Catarina, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Lemm, Sebastian, circa 2005 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Lempert, Talia, circa 2005 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Lendval, Thomas, circa 2005 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - leonardogillesfleur, circa 2006 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Leshem, Meirav, circa 2005 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Leven, Barbara E., circa 2006 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Levey, Jess, circa 2006 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Levin, Helen, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Levinsohn, Rita, circa 2001 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Levy, Alison, circa 2003 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Levy, Judy, circa 2001 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Levy, Nina, circa 2001 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Lewis, Bridget, circa 2004 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Lewis, Heather, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Lewis, Martha, circa 2006 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Lewis, Michael, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Lewis, Scott, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Lewis, Steve, circa 2005 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Leys, Rejin, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Leyva, Debbie, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Liboiron, Max N.M., 2008 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Lichau, Ajan Joy, circa 2002 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Lichtman, Daniel, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Licul, Danny, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Liddell, Vivian, circa 2007 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Liftig, Anya, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Lillard, Brian, circa 2002 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Lilly, Alex, circa 2005 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Lin, Jia-Jen, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Lin, Kay, circa 2003 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Lincoln, Amy P., circa 2008 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Linder, Joan, circa 2003 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Lindgren, Lisa, circa 2005 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Lindquist, Greg, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Liotchev, Ivan, circa 2006 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Lipan, Tai, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Liu, Jing, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Livensperger, Beth, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Liz-N-Val, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Llano, Maria, circa 2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Loefke, Andrea, circa 2003 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Loi, Valentina, circa 2002 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Lopes, Cyrianco, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Lopez, Elio, circa 2002 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Lopez, Michelle, circa 2001 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - LoPresti, Eric, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Lorenz, Hillary, circa 2005 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Lorenzini, Alessandro, circa 2005 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Loutrel, Lara, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Louviere and Vanessa, circa 2004 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Love, Robyn, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Loyche, Rebecca, circa 2007 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Lozano, Luanda, circa 2000 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Lubliner, Barbara, circa 2006 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Lucas, Matt, circa 2004 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Ludt, Ingrid, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Luib, Tony, circa 2004 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Lujan, Jason, circa 2005 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Luvaas, Lucinda, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Lynch, Janelle, circa 2006 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Lynn, Kristy, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Machado, Thessia, circa 2007 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Mackenzie, Chris, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Maczynski, Jacek, circa 2007 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Maddocks, Chris, circa 2005 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Maddox, Susan, circa 2006 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Madore, Ken, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Mae, Mari, circa 2001 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Maertz, Allen, circa 2003 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Magic Laser, Liz, circa 2006 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Maher, MaryKate, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Maher, Miranda, circa 2005 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Mahnick, Amy, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Major, Shawne, circa 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Mak, Caroline, circa 2006 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Makenzie, Alexander, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Makin, Jessica, circa 2007 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Malcolm, Dennis, circa 2005 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Malewska, Monika, circa 2009 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Malitz, Suzanne, circa 2008 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Mallo, Peter, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Manley, Michelle, circa 2004 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Mann, Julie Ann, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Mar, Kendrick, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Marco, Mitchell, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Marcuse, Michelle, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Marlowe, Glenn, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Margolis, Karen, circa 2004 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Marin-Arias, Hector, circa 2001 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Marion, Harriet, circa 2005 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Markell, Eliot, circa 2005 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Markley, Norma, circa 2006 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Markman, Grace, circa 2006 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Marquart, Carolin, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Marshall, Daniel, circa 2005 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Marston, Karen, circa 2003 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Martin, Greg, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Martin, James, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Martin, Justin Lee, circa 2011 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Martin, Thomas, circa 2006 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Martin, Katy, circa 2002 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Martin, Jesse Patrick, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Martin, William, circa 2004 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Marx, Kristine, circa 2003 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Marxer, Donna, circa 2004 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Mason, Jennifer Marie, circa 2005 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Masley, Caitlin, circa 2007 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Massey, Christina, circa 2006 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Mathis, Amanda C., circa 2008 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Matsuda-Dunn, Pamela, circa 2002 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Masui, Yumiko, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Mata, Justin, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Mathis, Amanda C., 2008 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Maue, Joetta, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Maurizi, Shanna, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Mavko, Eric, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Maxwell, Brookie, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Maxwell, Miranda Hellman, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - May, Jeanette, circa 2009 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - May, Rebekah, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Mayer, John D.N., circa 2001 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Mayo, Nesta, circa 2005 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Mayo, Sherry, circa 2003 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Mazur, Tereza, circa 2004 (Box 26, Folder 28)